Do what
Google wants
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
our clients who
are following the
things we're
telling them to
do
they're winning
and they're
dominating on AI
visibility and
they're actually
getting leads and
calls and website
forms into their
business from AI
so that's that
when I tell
people that
they're usually
like yeah let's
publish the
prices so most of
the time people
don't have an
issue with
publishing the
prices when they
understand what
it does but more
and more Google
is pushing people
towards showing
your prices the
more that you
show your prices
the more you're
going to show up
this is what
Google wants from
you
So the more you
do what Google
wants
the more they're
going to reward
you by showing
you first
which is really
the win of what
we're trying to
get and grow the
business